I want it to be classy and I want them
to feel really good when they're here
like it's a really good energy so I'm
super excited I want to start hosting
once a month female influencer kind of
networking dinners and so that's on my
vision for 2018 because I'm going to be
here in Miami until the end of May and
then I'm gonna be back in Toronto area
for about eight months U my brother's
getting married and there's a lot of
exciting things going on and I want to
be there when my niece grows up and get
to spend time with in person and then
I'm sure I'll be off to my next
destination wherever that may be woo
that on the relationship side of things
it's even more tricky um because and and
it's so weird that you ask me that
because today when I was getting out of
the
shower I literally was just having this
thought because I've been I haven't been
in a I haven't been in a relationship
since
around May or June and um I'm getting to
the point where I'm feeling like you
know what I'm really ready to have love
in my life again but I'm the kind of
person where I do everything in my life
all or nothing I do not take things on
that I'm not going to pour my 100% heart
into and so the way that dating works
these days is not really my jam you know
I'm not into that whole like meeting
someone and then they say one wrong
thing and you ghost them and all this
stuff like and like the whole I don't
want to get on the phone with you so I'm
just GNA text you for a million years
and all that stuff like I'm not really
so down with that I'm more like let's
get together and have the deepest
conversation you've ever had in your
life while i gaze deep into your eyes
and into your soul kind of
person um and that's not so easy to find
and so today when I was getting out of
the shower and I was thinking you know
what I think I'm ready soon to start
feeling like I I'm open to relationship
again this thought came into my my mind
as well that I'm just doing so well in
my business right now and so many ideas
are coming to me and I'm executing
immediately and really going for it and
I know myself that if I were to get into
a new relationship right now I get so
consumed by it that I end up spending
all my time focused on that other person
and I love the way that things are going
right now and I love love love just
having the freedom and the independence
to really like as soon as my mind thinks
of something I immediately do it I don't
let fear come into play because if you
keep taking action you stay ahead of
that fear and it can never paralyze you
and so right now it's all a game of
intuition comes take action intuition
comes go do it immediately just take
action keep moving forward and so I'm at
this weird place where I feel like I
really
am ready to feel and meet that person
that I've been visualizing and attract
him into my life but at the same time I
need to become mature enough to set the
right boundaries so that I can stay as
motivated about my business and spend
the this the right amount of time still
working on my business and so I'm
manifesting kind of the perfect
situation where I have another
entrepreneur come into my life who
understands the importance of staying
dedicated and committed to what you're
doing and what you're passionate about
and so um there's a question mark there
right now but of course um I my my power
of visualization is very strong and so
when I'm truly ready he will be
there I I you know and I I mean I I
spent four years of my life going
through that same thing um not liking
the you know it's convenient to go on
Tinder and swipe you know and swipe the
person but when you're having these when
because I guess as entrepreneurs we are
it is a spiritual process you know I
don't we we call it
entrepreneurship but you know we've been
creating opportunities before you know
there was you know without having to be
defined by makeup Etc I think that is
awesome you know it takes a lot of guts
to put yourself out there like that and
that's why I really wanted her to be on
the hustles on tonight was because you
know she is the she she is the
definition of someone that doesn't shy
away from being her true authentic self
so folks she is a
inspirational um you know she's a
motivational speaker uh she has a uh
she's writing a book she has a course
coming out and um you know she has a
challenge and we're going to talk all
about that tonight so I can't wait to
have her on so folks with all uh with
all due respect I'm sorry no more
yapping it's time to bring Lindsay onto
the screen so hi how's it going Lindsay
hello hello hello Ryan and everybody I'm
so excited to be here tonight on pule
Zone
TV awesome awesome so yes Lindsay um you
know so before we get into the our
actual format of the show tell us a
little bit about why you went like you
why why you went on camera with no
makeup like what was the the whole uh
Vision behind
that so for me um I can give you the
long version or the short version which
one do you want
both well give me the long version this
is your your floor
tonight um so when I started my business
my business was called the lifestyle
millionaire and it was a brand that was
designed for me the name of the brand by
a mentor that I had at the time and
although I was super excited about at
the time I spent eight to 10 months
building this perfect brand um it was
something that I was really proud of and
as the name of your show is I hustled a
lot to make it a huge success but I felt
really imprisoned by that brand because
I always had so much pressure to post
the perfect pictures and look perfect
and deliver the perfect speech and it
really fell out of alignment with me and
I fell really out of love with my brand
and I started creating things that were
focused on what would make me money as
opposed to what I was super passionate
about and super on fire in my heart
about and so when I launched my new
brand the hungry lius it was so led by
my intuition and I am so focused on
traveling anywhere my intuition will
lead me now
and honestly it's so important for me to
share who I really am and so I work from
home and so I'm not one of those girls
who gets up every day and throws on
makeup has perfect hair the perfect
outfit heals and walks my dog in heels
I'm just not that girl and so I like
showing the whole spectrum of who I am
some days I don't have makeup on and my
hair is in a messy bun and I'm okay with
rocking that other days I'm all doled up
and ready to hit the town ship sipping
sh champagne I go to fancy restaurants I
I travel the world there's this whole
spectrum of who Lindsay is and I'm not
okay with only showing the most perfect
parts of me and that being said right
now I'm on a mission to help women
female entrepreneurs develop completely
authentic Brands and show them that it's
possible to be wildly successful while
being yourself and so it's so important
important that I have complete
transparency and that I'm always the
product of my teaching and my coaching
and I always lead by example and so
there's no point of me discussing super
deep super profound things and then
trying to be this perfect news reporter
I am reporting to you live from my on La
TV and I will never show you the real
side of me because I am perfect you know
it it just people don't relate to that
and they don't want to be coached by
someone who's a Barbie doll and so it's
really important to me to be coming from
the heart not So Much from the head to
focus on connection over Perfection why
do you think uh why do you think that
people want to like especially on
Facebook live it it seems to be a trend
where people just post all the things
that are um you know the best things
about themselves but they never want to
to reveal some of the more intimate you
know details uh why do you think that
people do
that I think because it's so easy to
hide behind a screen and we have become
so out of touch as a society and we have
lost the ability to profoundly and
deeply communicate with each other and
express radical honesty with both
ourselves and each other and as a coach
I am extremely determined to help people
wake up and to really start
communicating at a deep honest level and
so it's really scary to put yourself out
there and really just show people all of
the ups and downs but in the coaching
world it's so important that you do that
because people are never going to learn
only from your successes they have to
learn from both your mistakes and your
failures and your ups and your downs and
your successes and the whole ride I
think of it as being on a roller coaster
ride you have those parts that are
leading up to a climax and then you have
those parts where you're speeding down
and you're so terrified but at the same
time you're excited because because it's
the most Wild Ride of your life and
that's what being an entrepreneur is all
about there are so many ups and so many
downs and loopd loops and it's important
that you actually portray the real
version of your life of course people
love to follow all the EXC exciting
things you do in your world and I love
posting them because I do a lot of
traveling and stuff and a lot of
exciting things but I also talk to
people when I'm home alone with my dog
on a Saturday night and I'd rather be
creating a sales funnel or a new course
than being out drinking you know so it's
all about balance and really just having
the confidence to be who you are in
spite of the fact that people will judge
you whether you're perfect or whether
you're a mess or whether you're anything
in between
now um people are going to get mad at me
if I don't ask you this question and
this is uh so we're going to start our
hustle Zone session and um you know this
is the first question because we
originally did this on the 1% it was
called the 1% jam session and um where
we were just tired of hearing people put
you know their their um their produced
material of who they are um and we just
said hey what's your story so what is
your story tell us from the very
beginning from when you were a child all
the way up to who you are now and we
have all night so you can go as much and
as deep as you want yay I love this I
love that you don't want to only ask me
about the story of my business that you
want to know the story of Lindsay that's
so different and it's so unique and I
love that about you and the way you do
your show oh thank you I appreciate that
so um I can't tell you from when I was a
baby because I don't really remember
that part
but I remember from about the age of
three years old so we'll start there I
was the biggest chatter box and just
excitable energetic little kid and
there's something that I've been doing
my entire life that I'm super super
super passionate about and that is
singing and so I've been singing since I
was three years old and I can remember
back then I would you know back then
there was cassette tapes and you would
have these um boom boxes with two sides
and so you could actually record the
radio and and record yourself singing at
the exact same time and I would uh I
would steal all my mom's cassette tapes
and record myself singing over top of
them and I used to have this little
microphone that was the same height as
me and it would have two buttons at the
bottom it would have one that was
Applause so you'd press it while you
were singing and they'd be like y
and the other one was people cheering
for you and I always loved to think of
myself in the spotlight and just sharing
my art with other people even from that
age and I didn't realize it at the time
but what I realize now is it's not
because I just want fame and fortune
it's because I want to use that platform
to make a big huge difference in the
world and I think so many celebrities or
people who are in the spotlight don't
use that power for good they use it for
vanity and so from the age of three
years old I love to create artistic
things and sing and perform and be in
school plays and all that kind of stuff
and growing up um I would have to say
I'm probably one of the luckiest people
that I know because I have the most
incredible parents in the entire world
they were always so supportive of
anything that I decided to do they were
never those parents who had unrealistic
expectations they would always say to me
that as long as I tried my absolute best
at everything that I took on that they
were super proud of me and I really
really really really appreciated that
and in fact I turned out to be the one
that was harder on myself than they were
ever on me and I've always really
appreciated that because they always
gave me so much love so much hugs and I
love you Lindsay and so much support
with my schoolwork and my singing and
they just both have done so many things
that are so selfless for me and my
benefit and when I think about
everything that they've done for me I
honestly just want to cry because I
can't believe I'm so lucky when I hear
about what some other people went
through when they grew up and I always
want them to know that I just never take
even one second of it for granted I
think about how grateful I am for it all
the time and I know that their love and
support is the number one reason why I'm
successful right now and why I've turned
out to be the person that I
am so um in high school I was I was kind
of that girl who was not super popular
and not super nerdy but just kind of
fell in the middle and I've never been
the kind of person that felt like I was
ever like super cool or fit in I've
always been really unique and when I was
in high school I didn't really see that
as a good thing because of course you
just want to be super popular in high
school um and I had an amazing group of
friends but while I was in high school I
was super involved with my singing and
so my mom was so insanely dedicated I
went to boarding school and high school
for so for the last two years of school
I actually lived there with all the
other people in my grade and it was
amazing and I chose to live there
because the school that I went to was
pretty far from my house and if I didn't
live there I'd have to be up at 5:45 in
the morning and I found myself falling
asleep in a lot of my classes so I ended
up moving there which was a good thing
because at the time my parents were
really really strict and the school was
not as strict as my parents so it's kind
of a nice little bit of freedom but my
mom was so dedicated that she would
actually drive an hour to my school to
pick me up two hours to another town
called Scar
brro and then I would have a 2our
singing lesson and she would sit there
and wait for me then she would drive me
an hour home because there was no
traffic by the time we were done and
then she would drive herself an hour
home and she did that once a week every
week for two straight years
while I was living at school wow and I
am so thankful for it because at the
time that was when I started my music
career and so I started writing and
recording songs and I started performing
in nightclubs in front of 5,000 plus
people and I started to hear my songs in
the radio and at 16 when that happens to
you you feel like the coolest person in
the entire world and it is just so cool
when you're in your dorm room and all
friends are with you and your song comes
on the radio and you all jump on the bed
screaming because you're so excited and
it was just the coolest thing ever and I
pursued my stinging a lot all the way up
until I was about 19 years old and I was
in LA meeting with record labels and
performing with producers who had
recorded songs for Michael Jackson and
Britney Spears and R Kelly and it was
really really really exciting
but at the age of 19 I found out how
ruthless and dishonest the people in the
music industry were and I totally got my
heartbroken by some people who really
made me feel like my dreams were so
close to coming true and they really
were but I totally got my heartbroken at
that age just by
witnessing
the I don't even know the word just
whatever however you describe how that
industry is just very a lot of people
looking out for themselves and looking
to make some money off of taking
advantage of people and so um after the
age of 19 I really started focusing a
lot on my studies because I went to
University in
Toronto and for four years you know I
did the typical University thing I was
on the cheerleading team it was super
fun we got to compete in Canada and the
US and we were the champions a few times
and I made some of my best friends on
that team I still have my very best
friend Amanda I met her while we were
cheerleading and um I loved the
experience of being in University being
away from home and really getting to
learn a lot of life skills I can't say
that I loved my classes at University
because at that age I really didn't know
what I wanted to do with my life and I
didn't find myself in the right classes
that really made me learn the things
that would have helped me right now in
my career but one really great thing
happened while I was in university I
needed a summer job I had been
Bartending for a couple years when I was
18 and 19 and you'd make pretty decent
money for an 18 or 19 year old but it
would never last the whole school year
and so by the time summer came in April
you'd always be with your last couple
hundred dollar in your bank account and
needing to make a whole lot of money to
support you for the next
year and I remember my second year of
University I didn't want to do the
bartending thing anymore
because I found that I've always been
the kind of person that's willing to
work harder than anyone else to set
myself apart as the number
one and um I found in the bartending
industry the people who would get the
best shifts and stand out the most were
the people who would flirt with their
boss and just be all sexual and stuff
and to me I never believed in getting
ahead by using your body I always wanted
to shine by being positive and working
hard and caring for something and
standing for something and owning your
right so that really pissed me off
because I was never willing to go into
those dark places to get ahead and so
one day I was at school and I noticed
that there was these bright fluorescent
signs all over the school all of a
sudden and those signs said make $100 to
$500 cash daily and I must have walked
by them every day for about two weeks
thinking it was the biggest scam in the
world before picking up a tab and at
that point I was like well you know what
I've been looking for jobs for the last
couple weeks and I haven't found
anything yet that's going to pay me what
I really think I'm worth and I'd like to
make $500 a day so I'm just going to try
this for a week and if it's a scam then
I'll still have plenty of time to find a
job before the Summer's over and so I
went to a job fair and I walked into
this warehouse and there was nowhere to
sit because there was 200 people in that
warehouse and there was a man at the
front of the
room saying to everyone that this job
was for people who are insanely
competitive who are insanely confident
in who are willing to have Blood Sweat
and Tears for success and who are
willing to compete against everyone else
in the room and rise up as number one
and I remember at the time I had never
been super confident I had been shy as
hell for a long time a really really shy
person and I remember standing at the
back of that room looking at that man
thinking I don't know if that's me that
he's describing I I'm not very
competitive I'm not very confident I'm
really shy but I do need a summer job
and I really want to make money so I
might as well just try this and if I
suck I suck and if I need to find a new
job I will but I'm not a quitter so I'm
gonna give it a full week and we'll see
how it
goes so what it ended up being was a
door-to-door sales job I had never done
sales before the most sales I had ever
done was kind of
upselling an like an add-on to someone's
meal at one of the restaurants that I
worked at and so I had no experience
with sales on top of the selling we
actually had to do the service that we
were selling so this is going to sound
crazy but what we were selling was lawn
ation so basically what that is is you
use a 300 pound machine that looks like
a giant
lawnmower and it pokes thousands of
holes in the grass the size of your
finger and those holes let water and
oxygen and nutrients into the the roots
of the grass and so what they would do
is there would be 12 of us in a van and
there'd be about 10 vans going out every
day to different parts of
Toronto and they would drop you off on a
street by yourself with one of these
machines and they would give you a map
and it would have two or three streets
highlighted on them and those streets
were your business for the day no one
else could go onto those streets and you
would be complet completely alone for 12
straight hours through any weather it
could be pouring rain it could snow it
could be hot as hell and anything in
between and you were by yourself with a
300 pound machine and no vehicle and
what you had to do is knock on doors
sell your service get paid and then keep
running and knocking on as many doors as
you can and they would come maybe three
or four times throughout the day to
check on you and refill the gas in your
machine but other than that you
completely alone and they would give you
a little training in the morning time
and I'm gonna be honest my first day on
the job my parents made me wear steel
toe boots how hard it is to run for 12
hours while pushing a 300 M pound
machine and steel toe boots those things
are so
heavy and I sucked I really really
sucked a lot the first day I knocked on
doors for 12 straight hours and I only
got four sales wow and first lawn that I
did it had been so long since the
beginning of the day when they trained
us on how to use the machine that I
forgot how to use it properly so for the
first lawn that I did it took a whole
hour because I forgot that if you
squeeze the handles it moves the machine
forwards and so I turned the machine on
but I physically pushed it over the
whole lawn and when I finished the first
lawn I thought to myself how the hell am
I GNA do this 10 more times I could
barely get through it the first time and
then at the very end of the first lawn I
accidentally pressed the handlebars and
it jumped forwards and I was like oh my
God I just did that whole thing by hand
when it moves itself forward
um it was a pretty dumb moment but it's
a hilarious story now when I think about
it and that day I went home having
worked the hardest day of my
entire life and I brought home
$34 wo $34
and I said to my
parents that was by far the hardest day
of my entire life hands down and they're
like well you're not going to do it
again are you and I was like of course I
am I said I was going to do it for a
week and I'm gonna do it for a week so I
think I took one day off to heal my body
because I couldn't move the next day
when I woke up it's like when you hit
the gym at turbo 10x speed when you
haven't been in a year like you use all
these new muscles
I couldn't walk so I went back the next
day and for the next two days I think I
did pretty decent I think I brought home
maybe a hundred $150 $200 which was
pretty good for 12 hours but then
something amazing happened on the fifth
day I started to get the hang of it I
have no idea what shifted but I think it
was that I started to realize that I was
actually really competitive and because
this job was quite
physical I was working with 95% men and
5% women there was maybe me and one or
two other women who would come in and
usually the other women who came in were
those super like Butch a athletic
women um who you know were used to
playing a ton of different sports and
playing with guys and playing football
with guys and stuff so I was really the
only girly girl
there and and it made me feel so
determined to think that I could kick
all those guys bugs and so something
clicked on the fifth day of that job and
I broke a record that was companywide so
that that location I worked at was one
of probably six at the
time and I broke a record for the most
sales that there had ever been in the
company on the fifth day of the job so
at that time the company was super new
and uh I mean the record wasn't that
high compared to what I did later on but
that day I brought home
$586 on my fifth day at the job and by
then when I made that kind of money I
was hooked right and every day what
happened was there was
10 10 seats 10 chairs and every night
the highest selling people the top 10
would sit in these 10 chairs and in
front of everybody in the room there'd
usually be about a hundred people who
would be working in that location each
day they would treat you like royalty
they would start at 10 and they would
work their way up to number one and the
number one person every day they would
hand you an extra $200 cash at the end
of the night and the whole room would
cheer for you and I loved that feeling I
loved it I loved being the center of
attention I loved getting that money I
loved everyone knowing name because I
was the best and from that day on I was
determined to be number one and stay
number one
always and what happened was
interesting started winning a
lot but they never would admit that I
was the best they wanted to make
themselves feel better by saying I was
the best woman at the company which to
be honest was really not that much of a
great reward because there was all of
five women at the company and I was so
much better than all of the
guys and so it took an entire year of
beating all of them before they would
say I was the best period not the best
woman and I was so determined to prove
myself and to show them that I had What
it Took and this amazing thing happened
totally by accident from my first month
on the job the CEO of the company had me
up in the morning trainings speaking in
front of a 100 150 workers teaching them
what I did to do so well in sales and at
the time I had no idea what I was doing
to do well all I knew was that I was
trying so insanely hard that I was
determined to run faster to each door to
get to more doors in the day to learn to
be better at air rating so I could do it
more quickly and I was just more
determined than anyone else and I worked
harder than anyone else and that was why
I was doing well but I couldn't sit
there and say that to them and so I had
to actually start learning about sales
and how to be great at sales so that I
could conduct these trainings every
morning and so every morning and every
night I'd be coaching and speaking and I
kind of just fell into coaching and
speaking and so we ended up having an
amazing first couple years and then when
I graduated from University the doors
really started to open to get into the
higher positions in this company and so
I started traveling the country every
summer helping to open new branches of
the company and train the new workers so
we opened up two locations in British
Columbia two locations in
Alberta and as I'd be living in
different cities for a month at a time
and I ended up living in Calgary for a
few years because the Calgary team was
by far the best team in the whole
company and as soon as I graduated from
University and started doing that
traveling my boss wanted more out of me
because he saw what a great role model I
was he saw how much I cared not only
about my own paycheck but about the
company and the success of the company
and so one day he sted me down and he
said Lindsay right now we door to-door
sales and it's Canada and we don't have
anything running in the winter time
because people can't be knocking on
doors all winter so I want you to come
up with something an alternate program
to run during the winter and it will be
your baby you will run it you will
design it you will train them on it you
will hire them all for it and so I
designed a program in the wintertime
where we sold toys at events that we
would run outside of grocery stores and
Walmarts and Home Depots and we would
sell toys leading up to Christmas and
when people would buy them we would
immediately get them to donate them into
our bins and then we would donate all
those toys to less fortunate kids at
Christmas and the program was a huge
success and we donated something like
75,000 toys across Canada it was amazing
and then on top of that I think we would
donate around somewhere between 15 and
30% of the of the sales as well to
different Canadian Charities so we're
doing amazing things and it was not an
easy thing because I had never run a
company before and so I was learning how
to develop training material and how to
manage the executives and the managers
of the company and how to do payouts and
payroll and how to do hiring and firing
and all the things that you need to
learn on the fly to develop a really
successful business right well it ended
up being super ridiculously successful
and I got promoted to the national sales
director of the company so for my last
two years of the company I would travel
around between our 11 branches for five
days at a time and just constantly
rotate all over Canada I would train the
executives the managers and the
employees of the company on sales on
mindset and I was constantly coaching
and speaking and there was me and two
other guys at the company and we would
travel all over together and we became
like brother and sister and we were so
close we lived together we worked
together and we traveled together
constantly and at the time we were all
super comfortable speaking and coaching
and we had great mindset and
determination and goals and we all
thought it would be a great career path
when we're ready to start working for
this company that we would go into
owning our own speaking and coaching
businesses and at the time we had been
watching Brendan brashard and he made it
seem like it would be so easy to get
into it you know we knew what we had
What it Took and
so the year before I quit at that job I
took a month off because I had been
working seven days a week for years I'm
talking 16 to 18 hour days hundreds and
hundreds of hours hours of work every
week I had time for nothing but work and
maybe six five six hours of sleep at
night and that was it and so I took a
month off and I went to an eco Lodge in
Nicaragua there was no electricity no
running water it was just in the middle
of nowhere and there'd maybe be like six
to eight guests at a time and all that
there was time to do there was read
write surf yoga and
play at the beach and so every day I
would do about two hours of yoga I would
do an hour of working out I would do an
hour or two of Surfing and the rest of
the time I'd be reading and writing and
I read nine books in that month and
while I was there I also wrote an entire
curriculum for four different levels of
workshops that I would run and the
entire outline of a book that I would
write H but what happened was I got back
to work I got another promotion and I
was at the highest level I could
possibly be at the company I was the
highest paid employee in the entire
company because I held two different
positions at the job I still did the
door-to-door sales Every Spring and for
the rest of the year I was the national
sales director and so I was the only one
in the whole company who worked two
different careers at the same
time all year long and and so all that
stuff I created went on the back burner
because I literally never had time for
anything else but work and I was making
multiple six figures so it was hard to
think about doing anything
else well what happened was the company
expanded into the US and my boss took me
and one other guy to help run the US
operations and launch it and train the
teams and while we were there I just
really discovered that my boss was just
lying all the time to all the workers
and he had done a couple sketchy things
with me and my contract for the year he
tried to take advantage of me even
though I had tripled his sales from the
year before in a thre Monon program we
brought in
$1.9
million selling five to $30 items in
four branches of the
11 and so it was insane the amount of
sales we did in such a short amount of
time and then he tried to pay me less
money the next year and then he acted
like I was being selfish for not taking
it and so that kind of set me off and I
thought you know what there's no better
time than right now to go just spread my
wings I know I'm capable of so much more
than this the thing is he made it hard
for us to leave because he made us these
huge celebrities within the company he
gave us huge trophies every year
everyone across the company knew your
name without ever meeting you they knew
everything you had accomplished
everything every record you had broken
and he made us like he put us up on a
pedestal but he would constantly put you
up there and rip you down put you up
there and rip you down and it was very
manipulative and so the day came and I
said enough is enough and what I did was
I bought a one-way ticket to Costa Rica
I went home for a week to visit visit my
family and then I got on a plane and I
went to Costa Rica I didn't know one
single person there and all I knew was
for the first two weeks I was going to
attend a yoga retreat and then from then
on I had no idea how long I would travel
I had an idea in my head that maybe I
would travel for about a month and then
I would come home and look for another
sales
job but I ended up staying four months
the first time and I had the best time
of my life
I had never felt so free and so
adventurous because for years I had been
cooped up and stuck at this job where I
had been working seven days a week 16
hour days and never getting time off and
so I had the most amazing time I felt so
incredibly free when I got there and I
ended up having to come home after four
months because my parents it had been
their dream to bring our family on a
safari trip in Africa and so we went on
this amazing Safari in Africa and it was
The Best Time Ever some memories I'll
never forget and when I got back I went
to Florida and took a a monthlong yoga
teacher training and then I decided from
there that I was officially moving back
to Costa Rica I got there I opened my
own Beachside yoga studio and retreat
center and I taught yoga and meditation
and exercise classes and I got to host
travelers from all over the world and it
was amazing I loved meeting people from
all over the world I I met some of the
most incredible people I had ever met in
my life in this magical town of Costa
Rica and it was so great for such a long
time but then at at a certain point I
just started to feel super super
depressed because it was a town of a
thousand people and for the most part
when people got there and decided to
live there it was because they were
wanting the kind of life where you went
to retire and kind of you know you had
worked really hard you go to kick it
easy drink beers every day chill at the
beach and for me there's only so long
that I can do something like that
because I was born for a bigger purpose
to achieve incredible things to make a
huge difference in the world and so I
started to get really really depressed
because for one thing there was a real
broke mindset there and it was so
surreal because at the time I had more
money than I had ever had in my entire
life I was well on my way to becoming a
millionaire but I had invested all the
money so that I couldn't touch it I
would get paid a small amount every
month residual income and I felt and
acted like I was broke because everyone
around me was broke and that was the
first time that I really really learned
that you are incredibly influenced by
the mindset of those you spend your time
with and so I was not broke at all but I
constantly watched what I spent and I
limited myself because I didn't want to
spend too much money because I wasn't
working a traditional job and I didn't
want to run out of money even though
that totally was not possible at the
time because rent and everything else
there was so much cheaper than living in
North
America and so I started to get into a
real rut and I couldn't get myself out
of it and I was super depressed but I'm
not one of those people who just sits
down and accepts it and so I started tra
like trying everything that I could to
get out of that state I would go to the
gym for two hours every day even though
there was no air conditioning in the gym
and it was like 90 to 100 degrees out I
would go every day for two hours I
started hiking and I started doing
meditation um grounding work and
gratitude walks and I tried
hypnotherapy and I hired a coach and I
did so many things journaling and
meditating and I even tried Iowa at the
time and I was so determined to get out
of this state but nothing was working
and So eventually I decided it was time
to move back to Toronto and really start
a new life and so I started getting
really exciting because my best friend
lived downtown Toronto and I had never
lived in a Swanky condo down there and I
thought it' be super exciting and it'd
be great to experience for a year and so
I moved back to Toronto and it was so
nice being close to my family again and
my brother had just had a baby
or my brother was just about to have a
baby at the time that I moved back and
so I got to see my niece being born and
she's just been the light of my life
it's just so amazing being an ant I
dreamed about it for so long and when I
moved back to Toronto I was so confused
about what I wanted to do with my life
and I ended up just to pass time and
figure stuff out getting a a serving job
at a restaurant that was near my house
for the first two months and although it
was a cool restaurant it was the most
negative environment
ever everyone hated their job and hated
the management at the restaurant and it
was just you go there you had been
having a great day and the second you
walk through the doors it was like a
dark cloud over top of you and so I did
not last any longer than two months even
though it was decent money and I I got
so lucky that
Facebook ad targeting is the way that it
is
because I thought it was fate at the
time I had no idea how Facebook ads
worked out but one day this ad popped up
on my Facebook that said we need female
speakers and just reading that little
little
statement had this light bulb go off in
my head and it all of a sudden I
remembered that I wanted to become a
coach and a speaker after I quit my old
job but up until that point I had
completely forgotten about it for three
years and then I ended up going to this
free seminar where this totally arrogant
guy got up and bragged about his $2
million watch and all his his Fame and
success even though no one in the room
had ever heard of him before that point
and I didn't see anything in him but I
saw something in one of the women in the
store stories that he told about you
know he tells stories about his
successful students and so I saw
something in one of his students that
reminded me a lot of myself and I
decided to just go for it and sign up
for one of his business coaching courses
and so I ended up working with a couple
coaches and it opened the door to some
amazing opportunities so I was super
glad at the time that I went for it and
it was amazing because about a week
after I went to that seminar I went to
go visit my parents and in a closet in
their basement I used to store all of my
stuff while I was traveling and one day
they asked me to go through my stuff and
get rid of a lot of it so there'd be
more room in the closet and I came
across this notebook and that was the
same notebook from Costa Rica where I
outlined all of the stuff that I wanted
to
teach and believe it or not at the time
I wanted to call my business lioness
Success
[Music]
Academy that's the first clue okay so I
ended up going to a little bit of this
business coaching seminars and this big
Guru who was on his way to becoming a
billionaire he looked at me he heard
maybe 30 seconds of my story and he said
your company is going to be called the
lifestyle millionaire and at the time I
didn't love being called that because I
actually wasn't a millionaire I was well
on my way to becoming
I was about halfway there but I wasn't
um I wasn't a millionaire and so it was
super awkward for me being called that
because people would ask me all the time
Lindsay are you a
millionaire and I wasn't and so it was
like having to play this hiding game
where I don't directly answer the
question but I don't lie and it was so I
hated it I hated it I hated it and at
the time I said to myself well this
guy's a billionaire so if he says that I
should be called the lifestyle
millionaire I guess I should be called
the lifestyle Millionaire right and
so I spent 10 months building up this
brand and I put everything into it I
worked day and night every day no days
off I was so passionate and the fire was
burning laser focus and I was just going
for it and I ended up building this
brand very quickly and before long I was
speaking on stages with famous
celebrities like
alucino I was interviewed for podcasts
and shows and on TV and on the radio and
everything was going so amazing so
quickly even though I had never run a
business before and I really had no idea
what I was doing and the thing is that I
got coached by some amazing coaches but
they only ever offered two days or three
days of coaching and you just can't
learn how to run an entire business with
two or three days of coaching and so I
had to figure a lot of it out on my own
and I scoured the internet and I tried
things and I hired people and some
things worked out and other things
didn't but what I ended up feeling like
was a lot of pressure to be perfect and
so I always had the perfect hair and the
perfect makeup and the perfect nails and
eyelashes and all this stuff on all of
my videos and when you watch the videos
from when I first started I sounded like
a news reporter because I was so
conscious of trying to put on such a
perfect show for everyone and show them
that I was an authority and I thought
that was the way that you did it but
what ended up happening is it ended up
being this Beast that just got away from
me and turned into something that I
didn't love anymore because there was so
much pressure to be perfect and so I
ended up creating this course and I'm
grateful that I did it because the
participants got an amazing success an
amazing journey and they got so much out
of it but I hated every minute of
creating it I had to force myself to
create the videos for it and it just it
got away from me and so while I was
right in the middle of a launch sequence
to officially launch that course
one day I was sitting at my desk and the
the hungry lioness just came into my
brain and that moment on from that
moment on I was so excited I immediately
saw the image in my mind and I
immediately got online and got someone
to make a logo for me and when they got
the logo back which is this one right
here you can't kind of see it um it was
exactly how I I envisioned it in my mind
it was so perfect my mind was blown and
all of a sudden I started writing like a
mad woman everything that the hungry
lioness was and everything that it stood
for and it was a really bad timing
because I was right in the middle of
launching this other program under my
old brand so it was the worst time ever
to think about launching a new brand and
I was right about to go to Sweden to
speak at a Women's Conference and was so
confused at the time about whether I
wanted
to go there selling something for my old
brand or whether I would have the
courage to get on stage and for the
first time ever announce this new brand
the hungry
lioness well here's the thing the hungry
lioness is all about courage and acting
in spite of your fears I help women
courageously walk through life saying
yes to themselves eles and their dreams
in spite of their fears and so if I was
going to officially launch this brand I
had to do it completely courageously
when I had no idea what I was doing and
I just took a leap of faith and so I
flew to Sweden I didn't know it at the
time but I was the only speaker coming
from all the way across the world who
was invited to be there from Canada from
North America every other speaker at the
event was from Europe and it was this
huge amazing thing and I felt so honored
to have been invited to be there and to
speak on stage in Sweden a place that I
had never been and if you know me you
know I am a huge travel bug I love
traveling anyone who invites me to speak
across the world I will always say yes
I've been to 35 countries en counting
every continent and so to go to Europe
to speak was an amazing blessing and I
got on stage and I announced the new
brand the hungry lioness and I told
everyone in the stage the reason that I
chose the hungry lioness is because
lionesses are not like lions lions like
to fight for dominance but lionesses
work together and I truly dream of a
world where women come together to
support each other to help each other
Elevate to tackle each other's fears
together and that's exactly what
lionesses do they are the hunters of the
pride and each lioness in the pride has
a different set of skills and T Bal and
they use them all together to accomplish
a goal which is providing the food for
the pride and they don't compete against
each other they help each other shine
and they realize that there's more than
enough to go around for everyone and my
whole life I've been watching women be
catty and gossipy and drama queens and
fighting against each other and
competing against each other and pulling
each other down and it was important to
me to develop a brand where women were
in the spotlight and helping each other
to shine and so that's exactly what I've
created and so I haven't officially
launched my first big official hungry
lioness course under the brand yet but
that's coming in mid to late
January but 33 days ago I followed my
intuition I had no plans to do this but
I launched a 45 day challenge I
recognize that so many people start
planning for the new year on January 1st
or January 2nd and what happens is they
set these New Year's resolutions and
then about a month later they start to
dwindle and they're left with no goals
intention or vision for the year and I
wanted to be able to put pressure both
on myself and on all the participants to
really start planning everything out now
so that by the time we go into the new
year we are changed human beings that we
would do all the Deep inner work to
really start transforming so that we
could move into 2018 as the women who
are in a vibration to actually attract
the very things that we need so that we
are women who are transformed but not
only that but super clear about our
goals about our vision and about our
plan to execute that vision and so I had
no idea what I was in for because I had
never done anything like this before but
I ended up setting a goal of having 20
women join the challenge and of course
when I envisioned something I have I
have absolutely mastered the law of
attraction I have come up with my own
version of it to absolutely manifest
anything that I want for my life and so
I envisioned 20 women in the course I
envisioned the exact results that we
would get and I could see it playing
like a movie in my head and of course I
had exactly 20 women enroll and that was
my cut off for the max because I wanted
to give them as much attention as I
could and 33 days in my mind is blown it
is insane the transformation that we've
all experienced I literally have women
who before like they literally used some
of their last $45 to join the
challenge I had one woman it was like
such a big thing to join she had never
spent money like that on herself before
and she could barely afford it and she
did everything she could to get that $45
to
join within the first 10 days I had
women taking on so many new clients that
they were buying themselves fancy
designer purses and BMW
I have women who have been getting
podcast interviews new clients new
opportunities to take on bigger roles in
their career I have had women who are
experiencing deep forgiveness with
themselves and people in their lives who
they were never able to let go of the
stories from before I have women who are
so clear now on their life purpose
they're making more money they're
feeling better about themselves they're
learning to love themselves they're Lear
learning to become the version of
themselves that they always wanted to be
and I lit want to cry when I think about
how amazing it's been and my only
regret in all of this is that I wasn't
able to help more people because I cut
it off at 20 and I want to be able to
help more people and so two nights ago I
was about to go live and I got another
Flash from my intuition and it told me
act now or never and so I pressed the
button I went live and I officially
announced that this week I'm launching a
7day mini course so that we have the
perfect amount of time to finish it
right before everyone goes into their
family holiday
celebration starts on Wednesday and it
ends on the 21st which is a few days
before before everyone gets really
intensely busy and in that seven days
we're going to be focused on getting
really clear on what success means to
you and what would have had to happen in
2018 for you to look back at the end of
the year and feel like it was extremely
successful and you were extremely
successful we're get extremely clear on
my exact methodology to attract and
manifest any you want in your life and
get it we're going to build a very
compelling future a a vision for the
future of
2018 we're going to plan out the exact
steps for what it's going to take to
accomplish your bigger your biggest
goals of
2018 and we're going to do some deep
inner work to learn how powerful
visualization is and to really start
learning more about ourselves and how to
actually create a hack or a cheat sheet
to perform better as human beings and as
boss babes in
2018 and so it's a 7-Day mini course it
starts on Wednesday that's that's in two
days from now I've already had think I
officially made the
announcement last night and in the first
night five women already signed up wow
and the cart will officially be open for
24 more hours hours and then it's closed
I'm going to cap it off at 20 people and
it's only
$47 that's the best part I really
recognized in my business that when I
was under my old brand I made my
programs inaccessible to people who
wanted to come in at at an entry level
sold anything less for three less than
$3,000 but I recognize that there's some
of the most incredible people who have
been following my journey and reporting
everything I do who just aren't at that
level where they're able to spend $3,000
yet on coaching so it was really really
important to me that I was able to offer
something at an entry level with the aim
that you will start learning to make
more money and then you'll be eager to
do more coaching with me when you can
afford to do some of these bigger
programs that happen later
on so this 7-Day challenge is going to
be open to both men and women it starts
on Wednesday night officially and you
have 24 hours left to get involved in it
and so if you want to get involved what
I'm going to do now is actually post the
link into the
group and um apparently I'm gonna do it
after the stream because I
can't I I just wanted to say that Susan
day um she says oh my God I can even
afford that I and and Susan I would
definitely recommend did you take that
course um because it sounds phenomenal
uh Lindsay Your Story I mean you pretty
much dominated the show you you you
really went in and and that's exactly
what we want because folks this is the
first living documentary we're
documenting the lives of entrepreneurs
and you know what Lindsay has been able
to do um you know she she didn't leave
anything off the table so um
someone's at the door I don't know who
but uh hey hey
Lindsay someone's at the door but either
way so while he deals with that I just
want to let you know that I just posted
the link into the comments and so if
this is for
you hop on it now and I will be so super
excited to go through this with you this
course is for you if you want to go into
2018 with absolute certainty that it
will be the best year of your entire
life and if you want to feel loved and
encouraged and
supported this is your
jam this is awesome so I'll put that
link up on the screen here look at that
so um folks make sure you guys check it
out uh I Lindsley I was expecting this
but you overd delivered on this you you
really gave us a lot of information and
you know and an inspiring like you know
you have people crying in the chats you
know so what you guys were all
writing um I I'm sorry I went so long
but you told me we have as long as we
want to yeah I said take take yeah this
is a part of the documentary and I hope
that you can encourage your friends to
share this post once we uh once we put
it up on our website and to to check us
out on our our podcast because people
need to continue to listen to your story
but I had a few questions and then we're
going to go into the lightning round and
then we're done for the day um so
question now I hear like within your
story and it and it is impower is
empowering um to hear all the things
that you've accomplished and you had a
great upbringing Etc but where did you
where do you like within all of this
where do you find time for relationships
and for friendships because while you're
building your businesses it seems like
you've been it like you know a lot of
this journey it's been just you just in
your thoughts saying hey this is what I
need to achieve and you've been really
you've delved right into just being a
like a mastermind you know like a almost
like a uh Fairy Godmother you're like
bity B Boot and then you just make
things happen but where where does that
stop and where does it you know where
does relationships and friendships and
and just nothing to to do with business
come in for
you um so before we got on this live
stream I promised Ryan that he could ask
me deep questions and I would be willing
to go there so to honor that I'm going
to go go there when I answer this and
not just give you some surface level
answer so there's two facets to it
there's the relationships and there's
the friendships so I'm going to start
with the
friendships I am someone who who
believes that it's very very very
important to always let the people in
your life know how grateful you are for
them how important they are for you and
so I made a rule for myself about a year
ago that if I think of someone I always
have to let them know right away that
I'm thinking of them so that they will
feel special and so that they'll feel
appreciated and so with the internet
being so accessible from everywhere that
I'm constantly traveling I've made it
important no matter what time zone I'm
in to always make the people that are
important to me in my life feel
special that being said it's really easy
to do over the internet and I've been so
incredibly blessed this year because I
have met some of the most amazing fellow
entrepreneurs through Facebook this year
and we've been on this journey together
and I've seen some of them pop up here
on the comments while I've seen a couple
comments come through tonight but I feel
so blessed to have been connected with
so many other people that are on the
same journey and for me it's not just
about other entrepreneurs what I
consider myself to be as a spiritual
entrepreneur I'm both spiritual in the
fact that I'm very feminine in touch
with my emotions in touch with um
manifestation and I believe in following
the energy of the world and the and the
moon cycles and all of that stuff and I
am very entrepreneurial in the fact that
you know I'm inquisitive and I'm
creative and I'm willing to work as hard
as it takes and I'm extremely dedicated
and determined but I find myself being
this perfect balance of both of them and
it's so hard to find that in real life
because people are either
entrepreneurial or they're spiritual and
the spiritual people look down on the
entrepreneurial people and the Entre ENT
preneurial people look down on the
spiritual people and it's like these two
different worlds that I'm right in the
middle of and so to be completely
transparent with you in my real life a
lot of the time I feel very lonely
because you're on this journey by
yourself and I almost feel tears coming
in my eyes when I answer that because
it's true I find it really hard to make
friends that are on the same path and on
the same Journey and who are willing to
sit there and have heart-wrenching deep
conversations because that's that's my
jam I I don't like small talk I'm not
good at small talk and when you try to
get me to do small talk I act like a
nervous awkward freak who cannot even be
myself and so I'm not great I'm going
out into groups of new people and
meeting them unless I'm in a networking
situation but friendship wise and I'm
going into a new group and I have to ch
chatter in small top I'm completely
nervous and in fact I'd rather stay at
home with my dog than do that and so
this amazing thing has been happening
because the internet has the ability to
bring us all together and to meet people
that are
super like me who are both spiritual and
entrepreneurial and in the last month
this incredible thing has happened
because I have met eight of them in real
life after fostering these amazing
online relationships for months and
months and months and so I took a trip
to California for two weeks I got back
about a week and a half ago and I got to
meet so many of my friends that I've
been making online in real life and we
had the best time ever together and then
actually last night I got to meet my
coach for the first time in real life we
met um I want to say like last February
and she's been coaching me since last
March and After experiencing what I had
when I first got into business I had a
lot of letdowns I spent money on some of
the wrong things meeting her was such a
blessing and we've always been so
aligned but aside from being a coach and
a client we've just become like best
friends and sisters and so when I
finally got to hug her in real life and
squeeze her and we kept poking each
other being like are you real like is
this actually happening it was just so
amazing it was so incredible oh my God
and so the answer to your question on
the Friendship side is it's it's not
something I've 100% mastered yet you
know I just moved to Miami and um I
haven't really had time to get involved
with much yet because I I literally have
been traveling so much since I moved
here but I'm finally ready to really go
out there and start putting myself out
there and getting involved in things so
that I can meet people and I'm really
hoping that through meetup groups and
stuff like that I can kind of narrow
down the pool to make sure that I'm
meeting like-minded people right and so
I meetup groups for entrepre female
entrepreneurs and I designed my home in
a way that I really want to welcome
people into my home I want it to be
comfortable I want it to be classy and I
want them to feel really good when
they're here like it's a really good
energy so I'm super excited I want to
start hosting once a month female
influencer kind of networking dinners
and so that's on my vision for 2018
because I'm going to be here in Miami
until the end of May and then I'm going
to be back in Toronto area for about
eight months um my brother's getting
married and there's a lot of exciting
things going on and I want to be there
when my niece grows up and get to spend
time with her in person and then I'm
sure I'll be off to my next destination
wherever that may be W that on the
relationship side of things it's even
more tricky um because and and it's so
weird that you ask me that because today
when I was getting out of the
shower I literally was just having this
thought because I've been I haven't been
in a I haven't been in a relationship
since
around May or June and um I'm getting to
the point where I'm feeling like you
know what I'm really ready to have love
in my life again but I'm the kind of
person where I do everything in my life
all or nothing I do not take things on
that I'm not going to pour my 100% heart
into and so the way that dating works
these days is not really my jam you know
I'm not into that whole like meeting
someone and then they say one wrong
thing and you ghost them or and all this
stuff like and like the whole I don't
want to get on the phone with you so I'm
just gonna text you for a million years
and all that stuff like I'm not really
so down with that I'm more like let's
get together and have the deepest
conversation you've ever had in your
life while I gaze deep into your eyes
and into your soul kind of
person um and that's not so easy to find
and so today when I was getting out of
the shower and I was thinking you know
what I think I'm ready soon to start
feeling like I I'm open to relationship
again this thought came into my my mind
as well that I'm just doing so well in
my business right now and so many ideas
are coming to me and I'm executing
immediately and really going for it and
I know myself that if I were to get into
a new relationship right now I get so
consumed by it that I end up spending
all my time focused on that other person
and I love the way that things are going
right now and I love love love just
having the freedom and the independence
to really like as soon as my mind thinks
of something I immediately do it I don't
let fear come into play because if you
keep taking action you stay ahead of
that fear and it can never paralyze you
and so right now it's all a game of
intuition comes take action intuition
comes go do it immediately just take
action keep moving forward and so I'm at
this weird place where I feel like I
really am ready to feel and meet that
person that I've been visualizing and
attract him into my life but at the same
time I need to become mature enough to
set the right boundaries so that I can
stay as motivated about my business and
spend the this the right amount of time
still working on my business and so I'm
manifesting kind of the perfect
situation where I have another
entrepreneur come into my life who
understands the importance of staying
dedicated and committed to what you're
doing and what you're passionate about
and so um there's a question mark there
right now but of course um I my my power
of visualization is very strong and so
when I'm truly ready he will be there I
I you know and I I mean I I spent four
years of my life going through that same
thing um not liking the you know it's
convenient to go on Tinder and swipe you
know and swipe the person and but when
you're having these when because I guess
as entrepreneurs we are it is a
spiritual process you know I don't we we
call it
entrepreneurship but you know we've been
creating opportunities before you know
there was you know what we would call
business because when you see a mango
tree in your front yard if you're living
in the Caribbean yeah you're going to
you know people are hungry you're going
to pull it off and they're going to
exchange things so that you know they
can have some mango I I think that we
all we've kind of lost this creative
mode we all lost this you know because
we go to school we get a good job and
then you know we get into debt and then
we're not inspired you know to be
ourselves so when you know you're dating
and I know this 100% when you're dating
people they don't understand your
culture and that's why I call it a
culture because you know they're like
wait wait wait a minute so you uh are
you still working it's uh it's 11:00
like yeah I am oh um so you you you're
you're trying to uh you're going to be a
billionaire yeah that's what I want
they're like oh
and they get scared so it's there's a
either they get scared or they think
you're delusional or they think that
your energy is so strong but I I
completely agree with you you have to be
in alignment with someone that actually
will accept that energy you know what I
mean because that's uh it's it's really
hard for people's Eagle to even come
into an environment where your energy is
strong cuz your energy Lindsay is really
strong I mean it's really hard for
people you know I I don't think people
would be able to to to get over you
because you you are so infectious and
you're you're so vibrant so I I can it
it's one of those things where I had to
decide earlier on in the year that I'm
like I'm just I I'm not going to even
put it out in the
universe what I'm just going to go and
create and I think that's what I do best
and if you just happen to bump into me
you know I'll take the you know I'll
take the opportunity but I think you're
right you just you have to we can't
think about those NE like cuz I feel
like when you think that you need
something you create that negative
emotion you know when you need someone I
mean like you need someone to fulfill
you it just creates a negative emotion
you just have to be in the state of mind
that you know what no matter if I have
someone in my life or I don't I'm always
happy one thing that I've been really
focused on right now while I am in
independent zone is um self-love
practices and so what I've been doing is
treating my self the way that I want to
be treated by the man that I'm in love
with that loves me love every I buy
myself a beautiful bouquet of flowers
and I take myself out on beautiful dates
at restaurants with amazing food and I
have written on my bathroom mirror I
love you Lindsay and every time I go to
the bathroom and look in the mirror I
look in my eyes and I say I love you and
you know there's a number of other
things I do with my journaling and my
meditations and my I am affirmations but
it's all focused on learning to love and
trust myself and we're all kind of on
this journey but it takes a lot to love
yourself in the exact state that you're
in and not put conditions on it I'll
love myself when this happens I'll love
myself when that happens it it takes a
lot of consistent effort to learn to
love yourself right where you're
at since I've been treating myself like
a queen I've noticed that all the men in
my life even though they're not in a
romantic capacity right now but all the
male friends that I have have been
treating me like they've been complete
gentlemen all around me they are every
time I enter the car opening the doors
for me buying me little gifts um you
know all all these little things that
show me like I am attracting people who
are going to be treating me like a queen
in my life whether they're a romantic
capacity or in a friendship capacity or
whether it's a random
stranger and I was always the kind of
person who was super polite and would
open doors for people and say please and
thank you and greet people and I was
wondering for a long time why a lot of
people were rude and and wouldn't do the
same things back but I realized because
it's not only about doing the actions
it's about being ready and willing to
receive and that's a big part of it and
a lot of us are such G
especially coaches and a lot of the time
especially women and it's harder for us
to receive right but as willing and
ready and open to receive so many great
things come into your life it's amazing
hey Lindsay so uh we are over our time
but we're going to get into the second
round of questioning so I don't know if
you're prepared for that but it's going
to be we call it the lightning round and
I'm going to get like lightning bolts
like but anyway um so we I'll um I'll
start with the first question so cake or
pie cake okay Godfather or Star Wars
neither how many times do you sneeze in
how many times did you sneeze in the
last seven
days zero zero uh do you do you like the
word
Dapper I don't dislike it
big dogs or small dogs medium how many
hours of sleep do you
need eight or nine um are women
complicated okay I didn't put this
question okay so we putting it out there
I think both women and men are
complicated I'll agree with
that um
and okay how often is or sorry how often
is it healthy to cry or yeah how often
is is it healthy to cry love that
question as often as you feel the tears
coming and you need to cry what's your
favorite carb bread pasta rice or
potatoes
quinoa that's a good answer because we
don't eat any of that stuff in the
house um if you could ask God one
question if you believe in god um or the
universe what would it be
wow that's such a hard
one maybe I would get him to teach me
how to
fly how do I levitate
God uh and
um stale Sour Patch Kids or fresh Citrus
peanuts or fresh circus
peanuts what so uh stale Sour Patch Kids
you know the candy or fresh circus
peanuts oh circus peanuts I thought you
said Citrus yeah sorry I I have dyslexia
so I see like random like letters come
up when I'm reading but anyway never had
circus peanuts so I'll go with the Sour
Patch
Kids and then the last question and I I
love this question and I've been asking
this every single time um and it makes
people laugh but is it wrong for vegans
to eat animal
crackers no no it's not so either way
thank you for doing the the lightning
round and then we before we close it out
um where can we find
you well um I most active on Facebook so
you can find my business page under
Lindsay Adamson
official and in a couple weeks I'm going
to be launching my brand new website and
so I'll leave it up to suspense right
now for what that is and I'll let you
keep watch on my Facebook page but feel
free as well to add my personal account
Lindsay Adamson you can see it on the
screen right now my name how to spell it
and um about a week ago I did a huge
cleanout so I do have space for about a
thousand new like-minded high Vibe
positive friends and so I'm super pumped
to meet you to connect with you and if
you guys want to join the course I'm G
to post it in the comments one more time
click on the link and let's have the
best
2018 of Our Lives awesome
and uh hold on one second so we have
like the comments are just off the
charts uh so we have one question from
Michael Crespo and he says so when when
you find a like-minded entrepreneur and
you're being busy on your business as
well as they are um how do you find
balance to give each other the time
needed to be in a romantic relationship
the question of the day okay I'm gonna
read that one more time because it's on
the screen
H well um I mean the last guy that I
dated was an entrepreneur as well and we
would go out to Starbucks with our
laptops and we would sit there beside
each other and we' both be working on
our stuff and um when we weren't in the
same city because we didn't live in the
same country we would you know schedule
time to talk every night and uh
throughout the day we'd be doing our
thing and working I mean I don't have it
mastered because I'm not with someone
right now um but I think that there's
one phrase that always sticks with me
throughout my entire life and I probably
won't get the quote exactly right and
it's not a quote by me but if something
or someone is truly important to you you
will always make time for them if
they're not you will always make excuses
pay attention to people's actions not
their
words awesome now uh Susan day asked
this question do you get depressed and
how do you deal with it I do get
depressed um I I don't know where it
comes from but in my life I think that I
get depressed when I don't feel like I'm
making as much progress as I want to I'm
completely addicted to growth and
progress and when I'm growing or when
I'm achieving I feel my absolute best I
feel my body buzzing I feel my vibration
and my energy High um so one thing I
notice in myself is every time I get
back from a big huge trip or a
conference or a speaking event I always
seem to go through two or three days
where I get super
depressed and before what I would do is
I would always feel really guilty about
it and and that I couldn't get out of
bed all day but what I learned was that
I mean and me and Ryan were having a
little conversation about this earlier
when we begin the journey into
entrepreneurship we feel like it has to
be all hustle hustle hustle all day no
time for anything else but what I
learned is when I go through those
periods of depression and they're gonna
come for a few days at a time right
usually at least a few days a month I
feel that way like I don't want to do
anything I don't want to talk to anyone
I just want to sit in bed and watch
netflixs all day and in the past I would
associate guilt and shame with them but
then not only are you feeling depressed
but you're stacking on top guilt and
you're stacking on top shame and
frustration and confusion and you're
stacking all these complex emotions that
you end up feeling terrible where if you
allow yourself if you say okay it's okay
that I feel this way I'm gonna give
myself these three days to do whatever
feels good to nurture myself to do
something productive that I wouldn't
normally do maybe take a bath or go to a
yoga class or take a meditation try
something new that's going to get you
calm and feeling
good and allow yourself to give into it
but only for a short period of time give
yourself a designated amount of time and
then decide that when you're done with
that designated time it's time to get
back going again and for the first day
or two that you get back going again it
could be either that you're like lit up
and energetic because you gave yourself
that time or it might feel like you're
kind of forcing yourself
but either way you get going and then
you know you start making progress and
it takes care of itself but it took me a
long time to be okay with giving myself
those few days in fact I actually gave
myself a day like that today I gave
myself a day off because I got to
thinking when was the last time you took
a day off and of course I didn't really
take a day off because I'm here on this
interview right now this awesome
gentleman and I've been answering
messages and making posts but I didn't
do as much work because I normally what
in a day and for me that's day off
awesome and you know um thank you so
much Lindsay for for coming in on the
show and thank you all that you know uh
uh I think it's Lauria uh Susan Lindsay
uh zanadoo everybody um yeah and and
sorry Dave da David Williams says can I
can I get on well um you can definitely
book time on the hustle Zone all you got
to do is go to
um hustlez own.tv
so go to hustlez own.tv you can see all
the interviews there um if you click on
living documentary and then click
contributors you can come on and you can
tell your story on the hustle Zone but
it's not kind of one of those shows
where I can just you know grab you from
the audience and bring you on um we're
working on it but uh you won't be able
to do that now and uh Lindsay thank you
for such an amazing Story You're it's
like I was talking to a celebrit you
know know like I it was it was awesome
and um I was just C I'm just sitting
there like I wish I had popcorn
listening to your story how was your
experience on the hustle Zone it was
amazing thank you so much I want to
thank you for creating an environment
where I felt safe telling my story and
um I just want to share a the message
with all of you that there is so much
power in telling your story whether it's
good or bad or or whether you've
experienced ups and downs it's it's
really important that you get
comfortable with telling your true
authentic transparent story because you
have the power to change other people's
lives for the better with your story and
if you don't tell it you're stealing
pleasure and Joy from them that they
could potentially feel by being
transformed by your story that's right
that's right and uh we have one more
tradition before you leave so I'm going
to do a call in response and I need you
to scream as loud as you can and I hope
there's no one sleeping um I live in a
condo so I can't scream too
loud okay well we'll try uh you know um
but as passionate as you possibly can so
I'm going to say welcome to the and then
you say hust
zone so all right so one two 3 welcome
to the hustle
soon I love it thank you so much Lindsay
for for coming in and folks holy moly
what a great interview she dominated it
like you know that's the one thing is
that we changed our logos at the hustle
Zone um because before it was a lion and
it had the hustle Zone had the lion in
the middle but I removed it and put a
plus because we want to expand and we
want to talk about more but reason why I
removed it because it was sending the
wrong message I removed it because Lions
don't do the
hunting it's the women that do the
hunting it's the women or sorry the
lionesses that do the hunting so when
you see my show open up and you see the
Lions right next to the Lions you see
the lionesses so um you know U the the
the lionesses are the the reason why
these lions are eating cuz all I see the
Lions do they just sit there and they
Roar they're like you know they're just
sitting there like this waiting for
stuff to happen and here you have the
lesses you know going after the prey and
and doing a lot of the work so I had to
CH what I needed to do is I needed to
change that narrative and tell the truth
so it was very interesting that she had
named her company that Lindsay named her
company um what she did what she named
it because you know it's important that
you know when you are I think in
business context matters words are so
powerful you know when you're creating
your Brands really take the time to know
what you're representing because when
you're promoting that lying for you
males you're promoting that lying image
all you're saying is that you like to
Roar but you know try to find I'm trying
to you know show people that there's
other ways to attribute you know your
aggressiveness and your your you know
your success and your achievements
there's many ways to do it but I think
that less is a perfect brand for for for
for for Lindsay's company because she
definitely demonstrated that tonight and
I'm super proud um that we like we
killed the show tonight like how many
people came on it was like 24 people at
a time I mean this this was was a pretty
good show and Lindsay and all the people
that that contributed to the comments
thank you guys so much until next time
I'll see you guys on the hust Zone and
if you guys know anyone that wants to be
on the show
make sure um you send them over to
hustlez own.tv we'll definitely like to
to talk with them and um you know and
they should be willing and ready to
share their story so have a good one bye
what if there was a docu series for
entrepreneurs that never ended a living
documentary that will continue to
clarify illustrate and unfold
information about the culture that
surrounds entrepreneurship what if this
docu series was filmed in front of a
live audience all over the world where
censorship and editing were no longer
applicable when information that is
given to you isn't packaged but
delivered to you raw and fresh honest
and truthful what if you could ask
questions live or help fact check while
someone is speaking well we have already
created this platform and we call it
hustle Zone TV
[Music]